

Natali Nascimento

Digital Experience Designer

I have worked as a Communication Designer in the past few years, developing several brands and proposals for print and digital products. I have a growing interest in working as a UX & UI designer and in developing products focused on the needs of users, constantly assessing the impact of the product through qualitative and quantitative user research.

Contacts

natali.do.nascimento@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/natali-nascimento behance.net/nanascimento +351 967 293 100

Experience

TerraProjectos | Graphic and Web Designer October 2013 - Present

- Working as a designer in a wide range of projects with different features, I had the opportunity to develop my skills in multidisciplinary teams and in close collaboration with the client;
- I have participated in integrated projects developed from end-to-end solutions, creating branding, packaging, brochures and flyers, international trade fair stands and brand landing pages and web apps.

E.S. Contact Center | Call Center Assistant January 2011 - February 2013

- Worked selling credit cards over the phone for Barclaycard;
- Had the opportunity to understand the frustrations and the needs of the "users". I have developed skills on understanding the sense of creating empathy with the final user.

MeioForte Promoção e Publicidade | Graphic Designer internship April to September 2008

- Designed graphic material for several events;
- Created and developed proposals for various corporate identities.

Education

Post-Graduation in Digital Experience Design September 2018 - 2019

Faculty of Fine Arts of the University of Lisbon;

I have completed end-to-end projects with design briefs, including user research, strategy, interaction design, wireframing, prototyping, testing and visual design.

Course in UI/UX Design & Development September 2013- March 2014

Edit | Disruptive Digital Education;

Hands-on user-centered design interactions, as well as designing components and designing interactive interfaces.

Master Degree Comunication Design September 2008 - December 2011

Faculty of Architecture of the University of Lisbon;

I Have developed my analytical and reflexive knowledge and skills, as well as the ability to problematize and think critically in a complete and specialized process.

Skills

User research

Usability testing

Interaction Design

Prototyping

Wireframing

User flows

Branding

Visual Design

HTML

CSS

Tools

Fiama

Sketch

Invision

Illustrator

Photoshop

Slack

Languages

Portuguese English